A Guide to the Farrier Family Papers, 1894-1972
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Box 4, 1903-1934 (Bulk, 1920-1929) (Box 4)
  - Lucas, Shelton E. v. Louemma Lucas, c. March 1925.
  - Martin, T. B. (Craig Co.), May 1903-May 1926.
  - George W. Meredith Estate v. Mary Meredith, March 1932-October 1934.
  - Mooney, C. M. v. Grand Piano Co., c. May 1928.
  - Esca Mitchell Exor Pearis Thompson, deceased, November 1926-October 1928.
  - Miller, L. L. et al v. Hinton Bank et al, February 1928-April 1929.
  - N & W Tax Matters, 1904-January 1928.
- Box 5, 1912-1933 (Bulk, 1920-1929) (Box 5)
  Files from the offices of Martin Williams and M. P. Farrier (abbreviated MPF). Subjects range from Norfolk & Western to Waddle, et al. 1912-1933, mostly 1920s.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. D. E. Conley, March 1924-November 1926.
  - Joseph G. Nash v. Erin Nash, September 1927.
  - Newport Service Station, Inc., August-September 1926.
  - Narrows Business Men's Club, December 1926.
  - New River Development Co., November 1924-March 1929.
  - E. W. Hetherington, Admin of E. B. Hetherington v. N & W Railway Co., December 1927-December 1928.
  - Town of Narrows v. Mary L. Dillow, March 1931-June 1933.
  - C. N. Williams v. Nannie Ould, May-November 1930.
  - Oak Flooring Co., March 1928-September 1929.
  - Dominian Power Co., October 1912.
  - James Perdue v. McKinley Reed, April 1926.
  - R. L. Peters v. G. W. Bradley (file empty).
  - Pembroke Bank v. R. G. Leftwich, et als, March 1925-April 1926.
  - W. D. Pearson--Bankrupt, March 1925-August 1926.
  - Arthur Peters v. C. W. Williams, January-February 1928.
  - William Purdue v. Commonwealth, January 1928.
  - Dan Perdue v. I. P. King, et al, August 1926-February 1927.
  - C. H. Putnam v. Peter Pfeifer et al, undated.
  - E. D. Phlegar v. Margaret Phlegar, March 1928.
  - J. E. Province--Bankrupt, July 1926-June 1926.
  - Rich Creek Development Co., June 1926-January 1927.
  - Litha Radford v. K. L. Radford (Bland), December 1924.
  - A. M. Robertson v. S. M. McKenzie, undated.
  - Robertson, R. W., January 1924-August 1927.
  - Snidow Mfg. Co. v. Cornell Wood Product Co., June 1927-December 1928.
  - Hattie Stafford et al v. W. B. Snidow, February 1924-October 1927.
  - Wiley Sizemore, October 1926-September 1927.
  - Eva Smith v. Olie L. Williams, et al, October 1924-December 1928.
  - F. M. Thompson v. J. H. Riggs, September 1928-December 1929.
  - C. H. Trusler v. Della Trusler, Janaury 1927-November 1928.
  - Virgina Limestone Corporation-H. B. Beury et al, March 1927-September 1929.
  - Va. Railway Co. v. R. E. Bryant, March 1929.
  - Va. Railway Co. v. C. P. Reynolds, et al, August 1924-October 1926.
  - Nora Vaught v. William Janey(?), August 1927.
  - Va. Railway Co. v. Town of Narrows (2 files), August 1926-January 1929; October 1929-April 1930.
  - Wilburn, April 1926-December 1929.
  - J. H. Wyse v. W. C. Burk, March 1925-June 1927.
  - Julia Waldron v. J. E. Province, November 1925-June 1926.
  - G. E. Webb v. Union Central Life Insurance Co., September 1925.
  - John F. Williams Estate, May 1922-April 1931.
  - J. F. Williams and Co. et al v. W. G. Albert, c. June 1926.
  - Waddle et al v. English-Ott Lumber Co., April 1920-April 1925.
- Box 6, 1913-1947 (Box 6)
  - Boggess, J. L. Jr. Estate, December 1934-May 1948.
  - Austin, Nelsie, July-October 1937.
  - Bank of Giles County, April 1940-July 1946.
  - Federal Land Bank v. Burmon Blankenship, July 1939-August 1947.
  - Federal Land Bank v. E. B. Conley et al, January 1926-August 1930.
  - Bland County Lumber Co.--Tax Matters, March 1920-April 1934.
  - Brotherton, Annie, Estate, November 1937-April 1940.
  - Bank of Giles County v. J. W. Williams et al, January 1937-June 1939.
  - Bluefield Supply Co. v. Cunningham Estate, June 1934-March 1935.
  - Mrs. Dorothy McCulloch Boggess, December 1934-May 1935.
  - Brooks, Russell, Estate, June 1932-December 1933.
  - Bland County Lumber Co. v. Virginia Hardwood Lumber Co., undated.
  - Bland County Lumber Co. v. Ott Rader et al (3 files), November 1934-February 1935; September 1934-May 1937; June 1934-October 1936.
  - Bank of Giles County v. Cecil Painter, August 1937-October 1939.
  - Bank of Giles County v. City of Bluefield, December 1933-December 1937.
  - Bank of Giles County v. Fount Johnston, May 1934-November 1939.
  - Bland County Lumber Co.--Correspondence & Stocks, December 1919-July 1928; June 1937-September 1938.
  - Bank of Giles County v. People's Bank of Files, August 1934-June 1938.
  - Bland County Lumber Co.--Taxes, January 1935-June 1942.
  - Buchanan Coal Land Corporation (2 files), April 1937-April 1939; June-August 1923.
  - Copies of Deeds, June-November 1946.
  - Commissioner in Chancery (M. P. Farrier for Giles County), August 1940-April 1945.
  - Copies of Deeds, October 1934-October 1939.
  - Craig-Giles Iron Company--Tax Matters, December 1913-August 1937.
  - Chandler, C. C. v. J. W. Fletcher, November 1924-December 1937.
  - Carr, E. S. v. R. V. Wheeler, June 1936.
- Box 7, 1900-1946 (Bulk, 1930-1939) (Box 7)
  - L. C. Corel and Wife v. Leona Spangler, October 1937-September 1938.
  - Dixon, H. E., April 1938-July 1940.
  - J. H. Duncan v. W. G. Gwinn et al, March-October 1940.
  - Dowdy, C. S. v. Dowdy, N. E, May 1938-April 1940.
  - Mrs. Cordelia Estes, March-August 1936.
  - Eaton, E. M, July-August 1939.
  - Economy Lumber Co. v. J. D. Jones, December 1939-August 1940.
  - Epling v. Epling, February 1924-November 1925.
  - Federal Land Bank of Baltimore v. C. J. Bowles, April 1936-January 1937.
  - Federal Land Bank v. J. F. Epling, December 1936-April 1938; March-July 1938.
  - Federal Land Bank v. W. W. Walker, November 1936-September 1937.
  - Federal Land Bank v. M. W. Reynolds, May-August 1939.
  - Federal Land Bank v. Porterfield, November 1940.
  - Federal Land Bank v. C. F. Straley, February 1937-October 1939.
  - Federal Land Bank v. F. H. Blankenship, August 1936-July 1937.
  - Federal Land Bank v. T. J. Blevins, March-May 1937.
  - Federal Land Bank v. R. G. Eaton, February-September 1936.
  - Hamblin, Easley E., undated.
  - F. M. Huffman v. Anah P. Huffman, et al, December 1936-March 1937.
  - Harless, G. W. v. William Mitchell Estate, January-March 1934.
  - Hardwick, C. A., September 1931-March 1935.
  - Hobbs v. Hobbs, May 1935.
  - Henderson, E. M. May 1936-September 1937.
  - Johnston, J. V, November 1935-January 1936.
  - Jones v. Jones, August 1935-January 1938.
  - Johnston, James D., October 1936-May 1941.
  - King, C. L., September 1923-March 1943.
  - Keith, Mrs Lucy (J. F.), April 1936.
  - Kelley et al. Trustees v. Gittens and Kime, July 1933-March 1935.
  - Lafon, Ernest B. and wife, August 1945-May 1946.
  - Lucas, W. C. et al, October 1936-November 1937.
  - Giles G. Lindsey v. Carson-Hayward Lumber Co., July 1925.
  - Long, O. E., January 1932-November 1936.
  - Lucas, Ora A. v. Mary Louise Lucas, April-May 1937.
  - S. P. Long Estate v. Clarence Syms et al., July 1935-March 1940.
  - S. P. Long Estate v. J. F, Maddy's Admin. et al, April 1938-June 1939.
  - Long, T. W., January 1937-April 1938.
  - Morris, J. L., September 1928-September 1937.
  - McDonald, April 1936-January 1939.
  - Miller, J. W. Jr and J. W. Miller Sr., March 1935-June 1939.
  - B. Mason v. Berwind Bank, July 1934-July 1938.
  - Meredith, Lacy B. v. Helen Hendrickson, December 1932-August 1936.
  - John W. Miller Jr. v. Ray-O-Vac, January 1935-May 1936.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. Wheeler and Chambers, June-July 1926.
  - Narrows Motor Co. v. Alfred B. Hare, October 1925-January 1926.
  - Narrows Garage v. Walter Perdue, December 1924.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. S. D. Sniter (fire claim), April-May 1925.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. East River Grocery Co., November 1923-December 1925.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. Martin and Lafon, July 1922-December 1923.
  - J. O. Johnson v. N & W Railway Co., July 1921-August 1923.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. W. L. Johnson, April-August 1917.
  - New River, Holston and Western Railroad. Co. v. Honaker and Honaker, April 1919-March 1920.
  - Narrows Motor Co. v. Cecil Casper, August-October 1924.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. W. P. Nelson, May 1927-June 1928.
  - New River, Holston, and Western Railroad Co., September 1900-November 1917.
  - New River, Holston, and Western Railroad Co.--Notes on Titles, July 1909-June 1916.
- Box 8, 1900-1930 (Bulk, 1920-1929) (Box 8)
  - New River, Holston, and Western Railroad Co.--Titles, March 1911-December 1913.
  - W. T. Ould v. G. N. Wiley, June 1910, March 1923, February 1924.
  - N & W Railway Co.--Eggleston-Berton Road, February 1926-July 1928.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. L. E. Munsey, February-November 1925.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. R. V. Wheeler, February 1916-April 1917.
  - Perdue, James v. Commonwealth, December 1928-September 1929.
  - Pittsburgh and Southern Veneer Mfg. Co., January 1906-December 1908.
  - Porterfield Lumber Co. v. Radford Grocery Co., c.1906.
  - T. J. Pearson v. H. G. Johnston, undated.
  - Pembroke Manufacturing Co. v. Kinnier, Montgomery and Co., February-July 1924.
  - Pearisburg Music Co. v. Mrs. R. J. McIntosh, April 1926.
  - Pennington case, December 1916-February 1917.
  - J. W. Porterfield v. W. S. Brown, et al., undated.
  - Pembroke Limestone Works, September 1922-January 1927.
  - Pembroke Canning Co., February 1925.
  - W. D. Pearson, June 1924-March 1925.
  - Pulaski Grocery Co.--Various claims, December 1924-October 1926.
  - Price v. Welch, October 1926.
  - Pembroke Limestone Works v. Commonwealth of Virginia et al, November 1924-March 1925.
  - Robert Powell v. Commonwealth of Virginia, June 1925.
  - Pendleton, P. C., December 1922-June 1923.
  - Mrs. M. C. Painter, August 1915-May 1916.
  - Mrs. C. T. Painter (see above file).
  - Porterfield, A. R. (Guardian) v. Mary Porterfield et al, January 1920-December 1922.
  - Porterfield, L. F., October 1900-March 1913.
  - B. P. Ratcliff v. A. C. Williams et al, May 1909.
  - Ratcliff, A. K. v. Giles Count Motor and Giles Hardware Co., September 1925.
  - Robertson, Ettie v. Grady Robertson et al, February 1922-October 1923.
  - E. L. Rice v. C. G. Brown, April 1922-April 1924.
  - Roanoke Hardware Co. v. S. L. Johnson, November 1923-December 1924.
  - Robertson, W. T. Estate, March 1923-February 1927.
  - Robertson, J. Hoge--Cemetery Case, June-September 1929.
  - State Highway Commission (2 files), August 1921-September 1922; December 1921-August 1922.
  - Snidow, F. E. et al--Election Matters (2 files), November-December 1927; December 1927-March 1928.
  - Shelton and Hardman v. J. W. Frye Lumber and Veneer Co., August 1927-April 1928.
  - W. W. Shumate v. W. S. Chewning, April 1924.
  - Skeens, J. O., October 1929-May 1930.
  - Strange Manganese and Mining Corp., June-October 1918.
  - Suffern, E. S. (2 files), October 1917-October 1918; January-September 1918.
  - First National Bank of Vinton and Scott Motor Co. v. S. E. Moss, August 1923-March 1926.
  - D. M. St. Clair, February 1906-May 1918.
  - St. Clair, P. F. v. Knepper and Good, June 1912.
  - W. H. Scott, June 1903-January 1906.
  - Snidow, Wirt B and N & W Railway Co., January 1919-January 1920.
  - Wirt B. Snidow et al v. G. W. Crabtree, December 1915-March 1919.
  - Snidow and Arthur v. Snow, September 1918-February 1919.
  - A. T. Shumate--Bankruptcy, May-August 1908.
  - St. Luke's Hospital v. F. L. Dunn, April 1921-March 1924.
  - A. W. Stable v. J. B. Brogan.
  - D. M. St. Clair v. Sara P. St. Clair, June 1924-January 1925.
  - Susan H. Smith v. Fry-Wysong, et al, May 1925.
  - G. G. Snidow--Guardian, November 1922.
  - Shenandoah Life Insurance Co. v. Hoge and Porterfield, October 1924-January 1927.
  - Mary Shufflebarger v. D. A. Smith, February 1924-July 1925. (See related folder below.)
  - Southern Auto Sales Co. v. N. E. Blankenship, February 1922-November 1926.
  - George Songer v. Commonwealth, October-December 1923.
  - State Highway Commission, June 1923-August 1924.
  - G. F. Stafford, August 1922.
  - F. P. Snidow v. Gilbert B. Price, March 1926.
  - P. G. Stafford v. Nellie Hearn Stafford, c. April 1924.
  - Peterstown Brick Co. v. J. H. Spangler, July-August 1927.
  - Shelton and Shelton v. A. E. Croy, July 1924-January 1928.
  - Spangler, C. W., October 1924.
  - E. J. Swain v. Childress, February 1924-August 1926.
  - Mary Schufflebarger v. D. A. Smith, February 1924-October 1925. (See related folder above.)
- Box 9, 1904-1929 (Box 9)
  - B. A. Smith and Hunter--Bland, August 1926.
  - Mamie Stowers v. Earl Stowers, September-November 1924.
  - Sharp and St. Clair, June 1913-November 1915.
  - J. H.Spangler v. Mary Brogan et al, November 1925.
  - Fletcher v. Strange Construction Co., August-October 1929.
  - Thacker Medicine Co. v. C. C. Thompson, February 1925-February 1926.
  - W. A. Thigpen v. G. Gibbs and E. R. Hill, August 1924-December 1925.
  - Union Tanning Co.--Tax Matters, December 1916.
  - Thornton, Geo. v. Cowlth, September 1925-March 1926.
  - Thomas Merchantile Co. v. A. P. Hunter, February-April 1925.
  - Eminor Taylor et al v. Josephine Taylor Duncan, October 1928.
  - Tidewater Railway Co., September 1904-February 1907.
  - Union Tanning Co. v. Narrows Water Co., August-September 1924.
  - A. N. Thompson v. A. R. Porterfield et al, September 1921-January 1922.
  - U. S. Fidelity and Guaranty Co., February 1914-October 1922.
  - Union Central Life Insurance Co. v. E. G. Lafon, September-December 1925.
  - Virginian Railway Co., June 1924-August 1928.
  - Virginian Railway Co. v. L. P. Noal, Admin., January 1926-November 1927.
  - Virginian Railway Co. v. W. H. Buchanan, August 1924-March 1925.
  - Virginian Railway Co. v. J. B. Ratcliff et al, August 1924-March 1925.
  - Virginian Railway Co. v. White and Cohen, November 1923-January 1924.
  - Virginian Railway Co. v. J. N. Deaton, March-June 1926.
  - Virginian Railway Co. v. Bertha Tiller, Admin., January-October 1926.
  - Virginian Railway Co. v. L. H. Fields's Admin., November 1924-October 1925.
  - Virginian Railway Co. v. W. C. Price (fire claim), May-June 1924.
  - Virginia Limestone Co., March-June 1916.
  - Charles A. Klotz-Ripplemead Lime Co., February-June 1916.
  - Virginia Limestone Corp., January 1920-November 1921.
  - Virginia Lumber Manufacturing Co. v. W. D. Carter, November 1914-October 1915.
  - Virginian Railway Co. v. W. R. Hilton, March-April 1919.
  - Virginian Railway Co. v. J. R. Johnston, May-October 1919.
  - Virginian Railway Co. v. K. S. French, February-October 1916.
  - Virginian Railway Co. v. W. H. Johnston, October 1916.
  - Virginian Railway Co. v. W. H. Thompson (Hopkins' admin.), October 1916.
  - Virginian Railway Co. v. Giles County, February-April 1916.
  - Virginian Railway Co. v. St. Clair and Harmon, March-April 1916.
  - Virginian Railway Co. v. J. R. Johnston, April-December 1916.
  - Virginian Railway Co. v. Monte Johnston, December 1916-October 1919.
  - Virginian Railway Co. v. E. E. Cook, May-July 1925.
  - Virginian Railway Co. v. Charles Ganoe, August-September 1925.
  - Virginian Railway Co. v. Motor Supply Co., May 1924-May 1925.
  - Virginian Railway Co. v. Clara E. Buck, November-December 1925.
  - Virginian Railway Co. v. Kissinger (road chance, Goodwin's Ferry), July-September 1925.
  - Virginian Railway Co. v. R. L. Johnston, September 1925.
  - Vaught v. Vaught, October 1925.
  - Virginia Grocery Co. v. Myers Motor Co., April-June 1925.
  - Virginian Railway Co.--Eggleston Road, August 1922-February 1923.
  - W. W. Walker, Treas. v. G. W. Huffman et al, September 1926-September 1927.
  - Ida Williams, admin. v. Virginia B. Williams, July 1926-June 1927.
  - Williams, J. F. (heirs) v. J. M. Kirk, July-September 1924.
  - Wells v. Wells, January 1925.
  - Williams and Farrier to J. W. Richardson, August 1912.
  - J. H. Woolwine (bankruptcy), March-June 1922.
  - Williams, W. F. (guardian) v. Billie Lee Williams et al, undated.
  - Wiley, Paul, March 1918.
  - Geo. L. Williams v. Johnston and Dooley, April 1908.
  - T. F. Witten v. Neel, May 1913-July 1914.
  - Warlick Furniture Co. v. F. L. French, c. May 1925.
  - J. W. Walker (committee) v. Keffer et al, March 1925.
  - C. W. Wilburn v. Bessie Wilburn, November 1924.
  - J. H. Woolwine (bankruptcy), May-June 1922.
  - R. W. Williams (4 files), August 1920-August 1922; November 1920-January 1923l April 1920-April 1921; January 1921-February 1922.
  - White Lumber Co. (railroad matter), June 1925-January 1926.
  - Wooldridge v. Jervis, January-February 1926.
- Box 10, 1906-1942 (Box 10)
  - Appalachian Power Co. (3 files), January 1924-December 1925; September-December 1925; January 1922-March 1923.
  - J. H. Wilburn Estate v. Appalachian Power Co., March 1925.
  - Appalachian Power Co. v. Kate A. Colburn, May-August 1922.
  - Appalachian Power Co. v. L. H. Johnson, July-December 1924.
  - Appalachian Power Co. Correspondence, December 1924-January 1926.
  - Appalachian Power Co. Papers, August 1912-January 1913.
  - Appalachian Power Co. Descriptions, April-December 1922.
  - Appalachian Power Co.-William Adair, May-August 1917.
  - Appalachian Power Co. v. Clarence H. Johnson, May 1922-January 1923.
  - Appalachian Power Co. (3 files), February 1917-August 1919; February-September 1923; February 1923.
  - John H. Angel, July-August 1922.
  - Appalachian Power Co. v. D. E. Dulaney, April-October 1922.
  - American Lawyers Company v. A. R. Porterfield, January 1925-January 1926.
  - Appalachian Power Co. (empty).
  - Army Draft, August 1917-August 1919.
  - Appalachian Power Co.-Deeds, etc., February-December 1922.
  - Annie Brotherton v. Appalachian Power Co., July 1923.
  - Narrows Fire Claims v. Appalachian Power Co., February 1923-August 1923.
  - Appalachian Power Co. v. J. A. Davis, admin., December 1924.
  - Appalachian Power Co. Ripplemead Extension, October-November 1925.
  - Appalachian Power Co.--Options, Narrows-Pembroke Line, February-September 1923.
  - Appalachian Power Co.--Pearisburg Extension, November 1922-September 1923.
  - Appalachian Power Co.--Notes for Abstracts, early 1920s.
  - Appalachian Power Co. v. W. L. Davis (3 files), March-April 1918; February-August 1917; June-October 1942.
  - Bank of Rocky Gap, October 1922-June 1923.
  - G. E. Barnett v. R. L. Barnett, January 1922-May 1926.
  - Brotherton, guardian v. Carter's admin., May 1922-June 1924.
  - Bolton, Mabel v. McGuire et al, 1934.
  - Bank of Pocahontas v. Helvey, September 1932-July 1937.
  - Martha J. Bowling v. Puckett, September 1924-September 1925.
  - Appalachian Power Co. v. Neal Contracting and Building Co.
  - Bland County Road Allocations, July 1928.
  - Blue Healing Springs Co., February 1911-May 1924.
  - Bland County Lumber Co.--Invoices, December 1919-April 1925.
  - Bank of Salem v. Robert Hoge, November 1924-January 1927.
  - Piedmont Business College, November 1921-February 1923.
  - Bland County Lumber Co. v. W. H. Bailey, et al, January 1922.
  - Buckhorn Manganese Co., Inc.--Certificate of Incorporation, March 1918.
  - William Brooks v. Louis Dale, December 1905-July 1907.
  - Bluefield Grocery Co. v. Harry B. Peters, August 1924-December 1925.
  - Bluefield Produce and Provision Co. v. Harry Peters and Atkins, August 1924.
  - Blue Grass Box Mfg. Co. v. White Oak Corporation, November 1924-July 1925.
  - W. A. Brown and Co. v. J. B. Brogan, January-April 1925.
  - Bluefield Sanitarium v. Lula B. Mullins, June 1925-March 1927.
  - C. E. Booth v. McCrosky, June 1923.
  - W. H. Buchanan v. C. H. Johnson, January-August 1926.
  - Frank Bane v. Lumberman's Reciprocal Association, January-April 1925.
  - T. J. Blevins v. Hugh Dickenson, et al, November-December 1924.
  - Bland County Lumber Co. v. Eugene Williams, c. early 1920s.
  - Bell Lumber Co., et al v. D. E. Conley, April 1925-June 1926.
  - Bland County Lumber Co., February 1917-May 1919.
  - Camp Manufacturing Co.--Titles and Correspondence (5 files), September 1906-October 1924.
- Box 11, 1905-1938 (Box 11)
  - Croye, L. H. et al, May 1921-August 1928.
  - F. H. Cunningham v. Conley and Dunford Estates, August 1931-December 1938.
  - T. L. Craft, May 1923-November 1927.
  - Crockett Mining Corporation, December 1917-August 1920.
  - W. C. Crockett (see also previous file), July-September 1917.
  - J. J. Cole v. Commonwealth of Virginia, March 1925-June 1926.
  - William H. Campbell v. Gibbs and Hill, July 1925-January 1928.
  - E. J. Carpenter v. A. R. Porterfield, November 1921-April 1924.
  - Columbia Chemical Corporation, January 1921-September 1923.
  - Mary K. Croy v. P. S. Croy, March 1924-January 1926.
  - Mary Chapman v. French et al, October-November 1925.
  - Champion Shoe Machinery Co. v. M. A. Jones and J. W. Stafford, November 1924-August 1925.
  - J. W. Clark v. Mary J. Clark, c.1925.
  - E. F. Chandler v. Lillie May Chandler, October 1924.
  - C and O Railway Co. v. H. L. Crowgy, February 1922-May 1926.
  - Cornett Hustlers Corporation, March 1922-February 1923.
  - C and P Telephone Co. v. O. V. Hopkins.
  - E. E. Cook, February-June 1925.
  - Roanoke Hardware Company v. Mollie A. Carter, October 1914-January 1915.
  - Adams, Payne and Gleaves Co. v. W. H. Carter, September 1915-February 1916.
  - J. B. Colt and Co. v. C. W. Atkins, October 1918-June 1920.
  - Cutshall, M. W. v. L. E. Cunningham, February 1924-December 1925.
  - Cunningham, Patrick J., March-April 1925.
  - H. F. Caudill, January 1923-October 1925.
  - Georgia Lumber Company v. W. D. Carter, December 1914-June 1916.
  - Deford Company v. Josiah Manking, March 1923-October 1925.
  - Asa Davis v. Mayfield Wiley, April 1926.
  - Belle Day v. Scott Chewning, September 1921-June 1922.
  - Deford Company, April 1919-June 1922.
  - Doss, John M. v. Mary A. Doss, May 1924.
  - C. L. Davis v. Leas and McVitty, August 1925-January 1926.
  - Andrew Dickinson, et al v. Clarence Dickinson, c. 1925.
  - Bank of Eggleston v. J. E. Province, et al, May 1925.
  - Bank of Eggleston v. E. M. Brammer, et al, July 1923-October 1924.
  - M. E. Epling v. Pembroke Manufacturing Company, September 1924.
  - E. S. Eaton v. Pembroke Manufacturing Company, December 1924.
  - Economy House and Material Co. v. C. H. Campbell, June 1924.
  - Epling, Minor, March 1927.
  - Economy House and Material Co. v. G. L. Morrell, October 1925-February 1926.
  - Erie Railroad Company v. Big Vein Anthracite Coal Company, March-August 1927.
  - S. L. Foster, August 1905-December 1913.
  - Wiley Faw v. C. C. Melvin, June-July 1930.
  - Federal Land Bank of Baltimore v. W. Arthur Snidow, March 1927-December 1929.
  - Roanoke Hardware Co. v. J. W. Farley, July-August 1921.
  - C. M. and R. L. Fuller, December 1922.
  - Tyler French Claim, may 1923-June 1924.
  - Flat Top Auto Supply Co. v. City Garage (Skeens and Davis), August 1925-January 1926.
  - Flat Top Grocery Co. Claims, December 1925-February 1927.
  - E. W. Frazier v. Walter Lucas, et al, December 1925-May 1926.
  - T. L. Felts v. H. M. Koller, April 1922-August 1925.
  - J. C. Farley v. C. H. Campbell, c. December 1924.
  - George Fleeman, August 1924.
  - Mattie Fraggitt v. Frank Fraggitt, December 1924.
  - Fayetteville Garage, December 1922-May 1923.
  - Giles County and Powell, Garard, and Co., June 1920-May 1922.
  - Gwinn and Brown v. C. C. Thompson, June-December 1925.
  - Aaron Graham Grocery Company v. M. L. Harrison Tie and Lumber Company, March 1921-July 1924.
  - Giles Lumber Company (2 files), April 1920-January 1923.
  - Giles Power Company, undated.
  - F. H. and J. B. Givens, and L. L. Lucas v. Kinzie et al, March 1923-November 1924.
  - Giles County Electric Railway Co., August 1906-May 1912.
  - Gwinn v. F. H. Cunningham, September 1924-September 1925.
  - Gibbs and Hills v. L. H. Fields, June-December 1924.
  - Giles County v. Lily B. Day, undated.
  - Great Northern Manufacturing Co. v. F. P. Snidow Co., November 1924-March 1925.
  - T. H. Gearheart, December 1922-April 1924.